

USER INTERFACE & EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

www.jackmercerdesign.co.uk hello@jackmercerdesign.co.uk 07546 115215

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a very determined and disciplined individual with strong technical design skills, as well as the ability to work on idea generation. My 5 years experience in the design industry helps me stand out from the rest; strengthening my ability to work in a team, enabling me to meet deadlines and work well under pressure.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UsTwo, Live Brief

January 2018 - March 2018

A live brief with UsTwo, creating a new product/system for Well Pharmacy. In a pair, we created a service that delivers advice to local communities. To demonstrate the concept, we created an application and accompanying advertising media such as posters & billboards.

James' Places

July 2017 - September 2017

For the summer of 2017, I worked in-house at James' Places. During my period of work, I worked on a range of promotional and advertising material such as posters & web banners, along with more hands-on work such as bottle labelling.

Atom Bank, Live Brief

March 2017 - May 2017

Working with the UX team at Atom Bank, as a pair, we conceptualised new ideas in relation with mobile banking, aimed towards students. The project involved idea generation all the way up to prototype, accompanied with a presentation to management of Atom Bank.

Sage One, Live Brief

October 2016 - December 2016

I worked with Sage One on a live brief for a university project. The project was to reinvent and redesign payroll. We used a combination of idea generation, digital design and prototyping the final applications. We gained excellent feedback from both tutors and Sage themselves.

Workhouse Marketing

June 2011 - July 2017

Starting through work experience in 2011, I progressed my way up to work as a Junior Designer. I initially took on roles working on print design, but then worked my way up to working as a key part of the digital design team. Working on Wordpress websites, as well as taking leads on digital design projects.

EDUCATION

Northumbria University

September 2015 - June 2018

BA (Hons) Interactive Media Design, currently in 3rd year.

Blackburn College

September 2012 - June 2015

UAL Level 3 Diploma in Art & Design: Graphic Design - Distinction.

SOCIAL MEDIA

in /in/jack-mercer

f /jackmercerdesign

@jackmercerdesign

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Suite (Indesign, Photoshop etc.) Sketch

Prototyping (Flinto & Invision)

After Effects

Premiere Pro

HTML 5, CSS3

Bootstrap

Wordpress

Ableton Live

PERSONAL SKILLS

Strategical thinking
Extensive idea generation
Big attention to detail
Project management
Strong interpersonal communication skills
Ability to work well under pressure

REFERENCES

Jamie Steane

Northumbria University

0191 0444523

jamie.steane@northumbria.ac.uk

Martin Meadows

Workhouse Marketing

01254 878956

martin@workhousemarketing.com